What is up with this ship?
That weird movement in rapid-fire magic cannon.
Does it mean...
Yes.
It seems able to process the human brain's reactions instantly.
That ship was made purely for war.
Commander, portside territory has now reached the threshold.
Redeploy territory.
And hurry up and recharge Mistleteen.
Affirmative.
Kanazuki?
Roger.
Commander, now.
Right.
Mistleteen, fire!
Man, that woman's got some kind of nerve.
Go ATR approaching.
Let me take care of that.
Look at you, using Adrifolium territory to bend the trajectory.
I'm impressed.
Then I'm honored.
After all, I could never allow our beautiful world tree to become damaged.
And besides...
Something else?
Rather than being on the defense, I always much prefer to see you as the aggressor.
Commander, Goatia's heading this way.
Help!
Anyone?
Is anyone out there?
Damn, what do I do?
I really don't have time for this.
Horikami?
You actually came back for me?
I'll regain the person I was by taking the life of Tokayatogami.
Please, don't.
You can't.
An unbreakable vow of revenge.
Once again, this girl takes a step into her own personal hell.
Please, don't.
Thank you.
What?
What's with you?
Your face is priceless!
Priceless!
Oh, this is hilarious.
I can't stop laughing.
Um, Kay?
Shido!
Hello?
What are you doing here?
How are you?
Are you okay?
Wow, well done, you, getting abducted in a secluded area.
Come on, Yoshino!
What are you waiting for?
Now's your chance to finally have your way with you!
Wait.
Hold on.
Be careful.
Origami's dangerous.
She's not herself!
Hey, uh...
I think that might be enough now.
What?
Hmm.
Natsumi?!
Yeah, what?
You complaining already?
Aren't you happy to see me?
Of course!
But what are you two doing here?
Oh, well...
I've been showing Natsumi around the city a little bit.
That's when we saw you and Origami out there together.
And, well, Yoshino couldn't really let it go, so we went ahead and followed you.
Natsumi, no!
You promised me you wouldn't say anything about that!
Well, anyway, this is great.
You guys, have you noticed I'm a little tied up over here?
Got you covered.
Please remain calm and leave me alone.
No!
Ivy is Morty covered.
Please remain calm and leave this to me.
Right.
Be my guest.
Natsumi?
What, you freaking shut up you little turds?
Thank you.
But, uh, what were you—
I recently realized that whenever I experience a negative feeling, I seem to regain a bit of
my powers for some reason.
reason any negative feeling yeah for instance during school lunch i usually grab food and eat
all alone in a bathroom stall since i don't have friends but then one time i forgot to lock the
door so of course a girl from my class came in and found me eating sadly on the toilet
that would be pretty embarrassing and then when i finally went back to class everyone was staring
at me snickering and laughing all righty i can't cope with this story time to go
this is weird i can't reach fraxinus wait a minute do you guys know where tolka and the others are
oh good are you finally awake
miko
urigami tobiichi monster what the hell would make you do something like this i don't understand
the question you're all spirits aren't you walking calamities that ruin the world beings which curse
humanity if i needed an excuse that's plenty so don't make me say it again
yuzuru this this is anguish why master origami why are you
let go of her you better get your traitor hands off yuzuru origami
kaguya
took a long time but now i have finally obtained it the power to kill spirits the power to fulfill
my duty with a single strike i'll reclaim who i was and soon all the spirits will be killed by my hand
in doing that i ensure that no human like me will ever be born again
urigami tobiichi
i'm too weak to do anything i can't even move an inch
but if i don't if only i had more strength i need more
no if i use that power i won't be able to save anyone
i have to be able to fight without losing who i am
to save kaguya
to help yuzuru
to make sure miku lives
and
even to save her
shito
i need you to lend me more power now
where did that form come from
origami tobiichi
i hate you and i always have
that hasn't changed one bit
but it's nothing compared to how i feel now
it's completely different
so
now i'm coming to kill you
do you hear me
origami
you'll hear me
get me
go
cut
you
I've got this.
We're evenly matched.
But with the power of this Mordred,
I can finally beat the spirit that killed my parents.
And then...
Activation limit...
Evenly matched my ass.
I've wasted my whole life.
It's all been spent chasing a spirit's power.
Since that day, I've sacrificed everything for revenge.
Now I have nothing left.
Nothing.
And for what?
Do you wish for more power?
What the...
Wait, what are you?
Answer the question.
Do you wish to have more power?
Absolute power?
Enough power to outmatch anyone?
Yes, I do.
Please, that's what I want.
No matter what it takes.
No matter what the sacrifice.
If you have the ability to give me what I need to fulfill my wish once and for all.
If I can wield a power that no one else could best.
Give it to me!
What is this?
If you want true strength, then reach out your hand.
It shall be yours.
Is this real?
What's this about?
Substantial spirit waves.
And it's a reading that didn't appear in the DEM report.
Seriously?
So you're saying that another spirit has appeared?
Strange.
And there wasn't a spatial quake.
A stealth appearance?
Wasn't Origami's so-called suspension suddenly annulled by the DEM, too?
What in the world could they have been thinking?
Toka.
What happened up there?
Well, once I realized I had to save everyone, my power seemed to come back.
Question.
Toka.
Where's Master Origami?
Last I saw, I was smacking her with the flat of my sword.
Which couldn't kill her.
And anyway, she's apparently got something called a teriyaki shield protecting her.
Teriyaki?
Correction.
I think you mean territory.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Miku!
You know, we really should thank her when she wakes up.
While you were unconscious, she literally defended you with her life.
Agreement.
She was admirable.
Wow.
Well, thank you, Miku.
The thing is, you can't really thank her unless you wake her up.
Oh, how should I thank her?
Isn't it obvious?
The only way to wake up a sleeping princess is to give her a big, wet smooch.
Oh, gosh.
A kiss?
Affirmative.
That's the idea.
Why don't you go ahead and dive in?
Come on.
Kiss her.
Hold on a sec.
I haven't said a single word here.
Agreement.
Neither have I.
Wait, what do you mean?
Miku, you're actually awake, aren't you?
Aw, man.
I wish you hadn't found me out.
And right when I was getting close, too.
You jerk!
Imitating me happens to be a grave offense.
Dang, that was pathetic.
Oh, sorry, friends.
Please forgive me, okay?
I promise I'll pay you both back in whatever way you'd like.
How about with my body?
Ugh.
Is that her?
Origami?
Confirmation.
You really think it's her, too, right?
It has to be.
But that form is something else.
Run now!
Toka!
I can't both fight and protect you.
Sorry, I can't help.
Blessing.
Go fight well.
Toka, Yatogami.
I will defeat you.
Origami, you little...
Metatron!
No way!
How the hell are you a spirit?
A spirit?
I see.
This change is nothing.
I will now wield this power in order to defeat all spirits.
I'll be a spirit-killing spirit.
And then, once I've eradicated all of them, I'll simply destroy the only one left, which is me.
Metatron!
Shinesh!
No.
Cheeto, look over there.
I think we found them.
I'm a monster.
Alec!
Kragor!
I, I think we found them.
I think we found them.
Origami, I'll ask you one more time.
Is there no way we can make things right between us?
I'd rather die!
My resolve will not change, and my mission remains the same.
Death to all spirits!
Every single one of them!
Fine, then.
I appear to have no choice.
Prepare yourself, foolish child.
Your punishment's at hand.
I've heard about enough of your bullshit!
Sandalphon!
Halvan Heleth!
Metatron!
Artalif!
Both of you!
Stop it!
Shido!
What are you thinking?
Please explain to me why you would do this!
Toka!
Origami!
Origami, come back!
I did this.
I may be a spirit, but...
The me I am now is finally capable of killing them.
Not just Toka Yatogami either, but Ifrit and Nightmare too!
Could it be true?
What if I really could make that happen?
I see.
So Origami's a spirit now.
I mean...
I don't really know all the details.
By the time she came back, she was already...
It's okay.
You should rest.
Hmm.
Are you okay?
Wow!
You really took a beating!
Nah, for real.
I'm good.
Big sigh.
Kaguya's faking it.
Shut up, Yuzuru! I'm perfectly fine!
I'm ugly and worthless and dirty like a steaming pile of trash.
But trash can be recycled, so I'm actually worse than trash.
She used a bunch of her power doing first aid.
Miku, don't push yourself.
It's really sweet of you to be so worried about me, darling.
But as long as I have some power, I still have a job to do.
What job is that?
Gabriel, now Requiem!
Hello and welcome, ladies and gentlemen!
You're in for a real treat with tonight's special show!
Miku Izuyo, now on stage!
Oh, amazement. It's like my pain is fading away.
This song's especially for pain relief. Not that it actually accomplishes all that much.
Thanks for that, Miku.
I know. Let's get you to the hospital while the song's still working.
Can you walk, Toka?
I have to seal her, don't I?
If the AST are able to detect her, they might sound the alarm.
What's bothering you, Shido?
Nothing!
But, uh, got a sec?
Are you okay? What are you doing?
Um, well, it's just...
Oh, I see.
So what you're saying is that right now, right here, we're gonna have to kiss?
Um, I...
Yeah, I think we kind of have to.
Hey, Shido.
I can't see anything.
Shh, you have to be quiet.
Could you please stop moving?
Where'd Shido go?
Everyone okay?
My goodness.
Itsuka? Yarugami?
Uh, hi, Miss Tamae.
Whoa! What a hideous injury!
Huh?
I'm afraid you need the hospital, not the infirmary.
Hold tight while I make the call.
Huh?
君と最後の約束をしよう
ooked by you
He needs my mind
I want you to stay
ㅡ
ずっとここで君と二人で
妖様流れる
星を見続けたい
君と最後の約束をしよう
世界から私だけ消えてしまっても
I'll ExperiAV ترك انه
Backing you with this feeling
And forever
My, my, my.
What a strange and unexpected customer we have tonight.
It's so very nice to see you, Origami.